[
    {
        "front": "はやし",
        "back": "森 \nforest",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんりん",
        "back": "森林 \nforest",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "こばやしさん",
        "back": "小林 さん \njapanese surname",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "りんどう",
        "back": "林道 \nforest road",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "もり",
        "back": "森 \nforest",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんりん",
        "back": "森林 \nforest",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "もりさん",
        "back": "森さん \njapanese surname",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちず",
        "back": "地図 \nmap",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "じしん",
        "back": "地震 \nearthquake",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちかてつ",
        "back": "地下鉄 \nsubway",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "とち",
        "back": "土地 \nland",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "いけ",
        "back": "池 \npond",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんち",
        "back": "電池 \nbattery",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "うみ",
        "back": "海 \nsea, ocean",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいがい",
        "back": "海外 \noverseas",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほっかいど",
        "back": "北海道 \n(place)",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいよう",
        "back": "西洋 \nwestern countries",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようふく",
        "back": "洋服 \nwestern clothes",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "とうよう",
        "back": "東洋 \neastern countries",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいせいよう",
        "back": "大西洋 \natlantic ocean",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆき",
        "back": "雪 \nsnow",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "おおゆき",
        "back": "大雪 \nheavy snow",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんせつ",
        "back": "新雪 \nfresh snow",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひかり",
        "back": "光 \nlight",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "にっこう",
        "back": "日光 \nsunshine",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひかる",
        "back": "光る \nto shine",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんこう",
        "back": "観光 \nsightseeing",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "だい",
        "back": "台 \ntable, stool",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいどころ",
        "back": "台所 \nkitchen",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "～だい",
        "back": "～台 \ncounter for machines",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "どだい",
        "back": "土台 \nfoundation (base)",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぜ",
        "back": "風 \nwind",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいふう",
        "back": "台風 \ntyphoon",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようふう",
        "back": "洋風 \nwestern style",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふうけい",
        "back": "風景 \nscenery / view",
        "chapter": "N4 K7"
    }
]